<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>gwax (Posts about waksman)</title>
    <link>https://gwax.com/</link>
    <description/>
    <atom:link href="https://gwax.com/categories/waksman.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Contents &amp;copy;2005-2023 &lt;a href="link://slug/about-person"&gt;George Leslie-Waksman&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;a rel="license" href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/"&gt;
    &lt;img
        src="https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png"
        alt="Creative Commons License BY-SA"
        style="border:0;margin:0;"
    /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:15:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
      <title>I just lost The Game</title>
      <link>https://gwax.com/blog/2007/01/i-just-lost-the-game.html</link>
      <dc:creator>George Leslie-Waksman</dc:creator>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Game was recently explained to me and I have been playing it since.
Sadly, just now, I lost The Game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>waksman</category>
      <guid>https://gwax.com/blog/2007/01/i-just-lost-the-game.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 03:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Non-Purists Perfect Frozen Margarita</title>
      <link>https://gwax.com/blog/2006/09/a-non-purists-perfect-frozen-margarita.html</link>
      <dc:creator>George Leslie-Waksman</dc:creator>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Having experimented with margarita preparation a bit this weekend, I
feel that I have come up with a perfect recipe for a non-purists
margarita. Feeling as I do about cocktail preparation, I have foregone
the use of the abominations that are premade margarita mixes but as pure
as my cocktail preparation intentions are, my recipe does not make use
of freshly squeezed lime, so I cannot truly consider it a proper
margarita recipe. That said, I think the results do speak for
themselves:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;/&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; cup Tequila&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;/&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; cup Triple Sec&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 cup (half can) frozen Limeade Concentrate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Margarita Salt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preparation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a 2 liter blender, combine Tequila, Triple Sec and Limeade
Concentrate. Add enough Ice to fill blender. Cover and blend. Serve in
glass rimmed with margarita salt. (To rim a glass with margarita salt,
take two wide, flat bowls, fill one with 1/4 inch water and the other
with 1/4 inch margarita salt, then dip a glass, rim first, in the water
followed by the salt)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Variations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As variations on the above recipe, the Triple Sec may be replaced with
any orange liqueur. Blue Curaçao, for example, will make for an equally
tasty but very blue margarita. Of course, Grand Marnier or any other
orange liqueur is also acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>waksman</category>
      <guid>https://gwax.com/blog/2006/09/a-non-purists-perfect-frozen-margarita.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 14:40:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunset on Neptune</title>
      <link>https://gwax.com/blog/2006/01/sunset-on-neptune.html</link>
      <dc:creator>George Leslie-Waksman</dc:creator>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I've invented a new cocktail, which I've decided to call the Sunset on
Neptune because it's blue, red and pretty. The drink looks different
depending on what direction you look at it from and your lighting
conditions, ranging from light blue, to deep violet, to dark red. In
addition to its fantastic aesthetic qualities, the Sunset on Neptune is
a very tasty and fairly alcoholic orange/grenadine flavored beverage.
The ingredients are as follows and there are a few different ways to
make it: (all quantities are approximate and should be varied to
personal tastes)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 part Vodka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 part Blue Curacao&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 parts orange juice soda (Polar Orange Dry, Orangina, or the like;
not orange soda)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1/2 part Grenadine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a glass full of ice (preferably large cubes) and pour in the vodka.
Add the orange juice soda and stir. Add the Blue Curacao to the mixture;
now if you stir, the mixture will be blue, but it you don't there will
be a thin green/orange layer on top with a slightly different flavor.
Now, slowly pour the Grenadine into the mixture; if you stir now, the
drink will be purple but, if you don't stir, you will have a red layer
at the bottom and a blue layer on top. If you decide not to stir the
Curacao or Grenadine layers, you'll get a really neat
red/violet/blue/green/orange/etc. thing going with a nice flavor
gradient as well. Overall, I'm fantastically pleased with the concoction
and would love to hear feedback from other people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I'm going to go out on a limb and speculate that the same thing
can be done with orange juice instead of orange juice soda and I'm going
to go ahead and coin that Neptune's Screwdriver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and if you've got a better name, I'm not married to Sunset on
Neptune.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <category>food &amp; drink</category>
      <category>waksman</category>
      <guid>https://gwax.com/blog/2006/01/sunset-on-neptune.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2006 06:13:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
